Nathan Denys

NATE_DENYS@YAHOO.COM (650) 922-0740 BELMONT, CA

SUMMARY

Adaptable team player with 6+ years of experience in sensitive, small business work-ethics, fast-paced environments, and a costumer experience oriented mindset. Successful at consistently delivering high quality service and going the extra mile to sell more and keep customers happy

EDUCATION

CODIFY ACADEMY
Front-End Web Development | 2017

UC IRVINE
Business Economics | 2015

EXPERIENCE

ZANETTE AVIATION INSURANCE SERVICES, INC.

Office Administrator | San Carlos, CA | October 2015 to December 2017

- Received client information and created specifications for underwriters to quote submissions
- Corresponded with insurance companies and insureds to verify applicant correspondence
- Reconciled and reported customer renewal information during weekly/ monthly meetings

TRADER JOE'S

Section Leader | Hillsdale, CA | November 2010 to May 2017

- Oversaw opening the alcohol section, became a small teams leader, unloaded product from trucks, and wrote various section orders
- Quickly adapted to different environments becoming a responsible and vital associate for all managers
- Clearly communicated with managers and customers to provide excellent service and effectively complete tasks

PENINSULA ITALIAN AMERICAN SOCIAL CLUB Bartender | San Mateo, CA | May 2016 to August 2016

- → Opened, maintained, and closed main dining hall bar for weddings, club events, and private events
- Quick with touchscreen point-of-sales and calculating checks and change
- → Consistently keep bar and work areas stocked, clean, and sanitary in compliance with bar standards
- Maintain a positive working relationship with fellow staff and management

SKILLS

Friendly Organized
Enthusiastic Collaborative
Leadership Responsible

Inventory Control Communicator

Self-motivated

Creative Thinker

Multi-tasker

Nathan Denys

DEVELOPER EXPERIENCE

WWW.NATEDENYS.COM GITHUB.COM/NDENYS650

 Continually progressing my abilities with working UI/UX practices and techniques utilizing HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, and VueJS. Front-End Web Developer, UI/UX Consultant | San Mateo, CA | 2018

- Worked with small businesses and teams in the development of their websites Front-End design
- Pushed to Github with GIT version control to work with other developers remotely
- → Utilized Figma to display prototypes to small business owners then converted designs into working HTML, CSS, and JS
- → Completed online courses for various computer languages to understand differences

KNOWLEDGE

HTML5 **jQuery** Flux Webpack CSS3 Git/Github VueJS **NodeJS SASS** Figma Vue-Bootstrap Rest API's Vuex Bootstrap4 UI/UX design MongoDB **JavaScript** ReactJS Vue-Router